Trying to fit in. Born to stand out.
What a Girl Wants is a comedy, romance, drama film directed by Dennie Gordon.
An American girl, Daphne, heads to Europe in
search of the father she's never met.
But instead of finding a British version of her bohemian mother, she
learns the love of her mom's life is an uptight politician.
The only problem now is that her long-lost dad is engaged to a fiercely territorial
social climber with a daughter who makes Daphne's life miserable.
Daphne Reynolds, played by Amanda Bynes.
Henry Dashwood, played by Colin Firth.
Libby Reynolds, played by Kelly Preston.
Jocelyn Dashwood, played by Eileen Atkins.
Glynnis Payne, played by Anna Chancellor.
Alistair Payne, played by Jonathan Pryce.
What a Girl Wants is a 2003 American teen comedy film directed by Dennie
Gordon and written by Jenny Bicks and Elizabeth Chandler.
Based on the 1955 play The Reluctant Debutante by William Douglas-Home, it is the second adaptation for the screen of this
work and stars Amanda Bynes, Colin Firth, Kelly Preston, Eileen Atkins, Anna Chancellor, and Jonathan Pryce.
The film tells the story of a seventeen-year-old girl who goes to
the United Kingdom to meet the father she never knew.
The film was released by Warner Bros.
Pictures on April 4, 2003, received mixed reviews from critics and
grossed $51 million worldwide against a $25 million budget.
The film explores themes of daughter, london, england, england,
parent child relationship, election campaign.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.